bigideamastermind.com 2015-06-02

# Big Idea Mastermind | Privacy Policy

Our company collects information in different ways from new affiliates and members who opt-in to our program. We use this information solely to provide affiliates and members with our products and services. We do not, under any circumstance, disclose personal information collected.

**Registration:** Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), SSN. The personal information collected from members during the registration process is used to deliver products. This information is not shared with third parties. Social Security Numbers are collected for tax purposes. This information is held with extreme confidentiality on a computer disconnected from any kind of internet service.

**Online Shopping:** At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information.

If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient’s name, address, and phone number. Our company has no control over the third parties’ use of any personal information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so.

If you order services or products directly from our company we will use the personal information you provide only to process that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

**Responses to Email Inquiries:** When visitors or members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys:** We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our customer surveys is voluntary.

**Public Forums:** Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

**Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy:**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practiced described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this web site.

**Revisions to This Policy:** Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time in any manner, by updating this posting.
